Here is another couple of examples of what the Holga does, and does fairly well.
This is an image taken with the Holga with a flash, very cloudy day.
This is actually one of the original munchkins from the Wizard of Oz.
And the Holga tends to make strange situations or strange images even stranger.
And that's sort of what I feel it did in this image.
It just really looks, really...the flash hit her, and just really made a very interesting image.
And also this image - the Holga tends to do something to backgrounds, where it flattens them out, and that has a lot to do with the aperture that is in the Holga.
But it also, it just makes things look like a movie still, which I find it does again and again and again.
And it's sort of back to that Holga being a one-trick pony sort of thing.
And it actually, you know, if you utilize it properly, it's an absolutely amazing tool.
So again, the subject is just right in front, and then the background, the people there, it just is completely flattened out, almost like that's a painting or a backdrop behind her, or him.